Andrés José Caicedo Cabrera

Colombia, Bogota | +57 3054276262 | ajcaicedo007@gmail.com / ajcaicedo@yahoo.com_ https://www.linkedin.com/in/andres-caicedo-7270a5185/ -https://github.com/Ruukazu

Data analyst and Full Stack developer with background in software analysis, mobile application design, database administration, cleaning and use of databases using AppScript and datastudio as well as different process management developments that helped me work as a team, analyze massive data, understand different work environments, participate in different projects, both in programming structure and data processing, and adapt to different work cultures to achieve the desired objectives. ANDspecialized in Back End, Knowledge in agile methodologies, GIT, data structure, algorithms, CSS frameworks, data structure, data collection/purification and analysis. Experience in Front End and Back End development / data architecture, Data Science with Python, JS, React, Node, GitHub, Excel, SQL, PowerBI, Sequelize. With the ability to communicate naturally in any work environment; outstanding analytical skills; ability to work as a team and under pressure; leadership and initiative. English Level: Intermediate English B2.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - PIVideoGames

Academic experience. Henry Bootcamp

November, 2023 - December, 2023

Web page designed with JS with the purpose of showing different video games brought from a rawg API, filtering, pagination, creation and search as well as other utilities and a basic design for its presentation. Likewise, in a larger project, we worked on the creation of a platform for managing student enrollment for a school that remained in deploy and is available.

Front: React-Redux Back: Axios-Express-Node

Database: PostgreSQL and Sequelize. https://github.com/Ruukazu/PIVideoH https://front-kappa-one.vercel.app/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Analyst

ESAN University

Feb. 2018 - May. 2018.

- Preparation of software documentation and modeling diagrams.
- Development of database models.
- Graphical application designer available for Android using IONIC SDK.
- Assistant developer using Python and javascript.

Postgraduate Commercial Area Professional

Dec. 2021 - Mar. 2023.

ESAN University

- Preparation of a manual for the area's private administrative system. (Web Development using HUGO Framework)
- Administration and development of area processes according to provided requirements.
- Responsible for delivering base financing for the Finance area.
- Database administration in Excel and support to the commercial intelligence area in SQL functions.
- Support for requests for advisors in relation to the administrative system.
- Knowledge and support about the administrative system to the main programmer (Python3).
- Handling by request of massive messages in both text and html format.
- In charge of creating statisticians and statisticians for evaluating the results of different campaigns.
- Automation of financing processes through the use of APPS SCRIPT AND VBA.

OTHER EXPERIENCES

Video game development workshop Boston

July 2023

High School.

- Teaching Unreal Engine for children. Using interactive tools and activities
- Development of basic classes.
- Basic game development with UE version 5.
- Teaching 35 students divided into two specific classes.

International Office Pre-Intern ESAN

Mar. 2019 - Nov. 2019.

University

- Preparation of database to support the area.
- Document translation.
- Maintenance and updating of data documents managed in the area.
- Prepare, organize and schedule meetings for the authorities responsible for the area with ESAN directors and foreign visitors from other universities.
- Participation in international events held by the area.
- Management of various documents.
- Sending and receiving documents or promotional merchandise.
- Preparation of database diagrams in Access and SQL.
- Assistant in all events held.

Software Analyst

Feb. 2018 - May. 2018.

ESAN University

- Preparation of software documentation and modeling diagrams.
- Development of database models.
- Graphical application designer available for Android using IONIC SDK.
- Assistant developer using Python and javascript.

TECHNOLOGIES:

Programming languages:|avascript, Python, R, APPScript, VBA.

Framework Tools:React, Express, Node. **Database:** SQL, QilkView **Tools:**Git, Basecamp, Slack, Trello. **Agile:** Scrum.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

- Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours of theoretical-practical courses. 2023.
- Bachelor in Systems Engineering. ESAN University. 2014 2021.
- Third year of Systems. SanBuenaventura University. 2013.

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

- Complete Excel: From Beginner to Advanced. Udemy. 2021.
- E-commerce Platforms & Content Certificate, GIT Certificate, Database Certificate. NextU. 2020.
- Advanced Google Analytics. 2023.
- 3D Object Modeling Course 2014
- Illustrator course 2014

LANGUAGES

- English B2 Intermediate.
- Basic Japanese Katakana-Hiragana
- Basic Portuguese
- Native Spanish